siteworthchecker.com 2012-05-29

# SiteWorthChecker.com - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not linked to any information that is personally identifiable) about your visits to our website and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

\- Google uses a so called DART cookie that enables the serving of ads to users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.

\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/

Collection of Personal Information

When visiting SiteWorthChecker.com, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links to third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

Visitor Communication

If you subscribe to our Newsletter and receive information from Site Worth Checker, you are able to unsubscribe from future communication with Site Worth Checker by unsubscribing from our mass emailing database or just emailing us (info@siteworthchecker.com) and requesting to do so.
